{
	"1679602249385": [
		{
			"name": "Czech literary authors",
			"description": "One book per author.",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "Válka s Mloky",
					"answer": "Karel Čapek"
				},
				{
					"question": "Křest svatého Vladimíra",
					"answer": "Karel Havlíček Borovský "
				},
				{
					"question": "Povídky malostranské",
					"answer": "Jan Neruda"
				},
				{
					"question": "Proces",
					"answer": "Franz Kafka"
				},
				{
					"question": "Těžká hodina",
					"answer": "Jiří Wolker"
				},
				{
					"question": "Tajemné dálky",
					"answer": "Otokar Březina"
				},
				{
					"question": "Babička",
					"answer": "Božena Němcová"
				},
				{
					"question": "Temno",
					"answer": "Alois Jirásek"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Periodic table elements",
			"description": "A set with elements from the periodic table.",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "H",
					"answer": "Hydrogen"
				},
				{
					"question": "Li",
					"answer": "Lithium"
				},
				{
					"question": "K",
					"answer": "Potassium"
				},
				{
					"question": "Sc",
					"answer": "Scandium"
				},
				{
					"question": "P",
					"answer": "Phosphorus"
				},
				{
					"question": "Pt",
					"answer": "Platinum"
				}
			]
		}
	]
}